Betty Wilke Cox papers, Inclusive: 1896-2007, undated, Bulk: 1970-2006, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Hudman Editing Service/Woodburner Press, 1985-2006; 1
  - Clients, 1988-2006; 1
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (13 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (14 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (15 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (16 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (17 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (18 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (19 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (20 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (21 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (22 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (23 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (24 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (25 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (26 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (27 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (28 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (29 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (30 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (31 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (32 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (33 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (1 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (2 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (3 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (4 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (5 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (6 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (7 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (8 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (9 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Will: General Research (10 of 10), undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Will: Tapes (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Will: Tapes (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Will: Various Partial Manuscripts (1 of 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Will: Various Partial Manuscripts (2 of 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Will: Various Partial Manuscripts (3 of 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Will: Various Partial Manuscripts (4 of 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Will: Various Partial Manuscripts (5 of 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (1 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (2 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (3 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (4 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (5 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (6 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (7 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (8 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (9 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (10 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (11 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (12 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (13 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (14 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (15 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Will: The Will to Win: Manuscript (16 of 16), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Complete Book (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Complete Book (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Promotional Material, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Sales Reports (1 of 3), 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Sales Reports (2 of 3), 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Wood, John: Texas Ranger in the Oil Patch: Sales Reports (3 of 3), 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Yaun, Ellen: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Yaun, Ellen: Illustrations (1 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Yaun, Ellen: Illustrations (2 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Other, 1985-2007; 2
    - Blackwell, Judith Morgan: Invoices (1 of 2), 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Blackwell, Judith Morgan: Invoices (2 of 2), 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Booklists, 1994-2005 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bookmaking, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Client Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Customer List, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1995-2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1995-2006 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Hervey's Booklink, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Invoices (1 of 2), 1989-2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Invoices (2 of 2), 1989-2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Newsletter (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Newsletter (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Research (1 of 3), 1996-2005 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Research (2 of 3), 1996-2005 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Research (3 of 3), 1996-2005 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Hudman Editing Service: Service Description, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mailing List, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Morgan Printing (1 of 5), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Morgan Printing (2 of 5), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Morgan Printing (3 of 5), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Morgan Printing (4 of 5), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Morgan Printing (5 of 5), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Non-Traditional Students' Organization, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Potential Clients, 1991-2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Resources (1 of 2), 1985-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Resources (2 of 2), 1985-1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Sales Tax and Use Tax Permit, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Short Story: Unknown Author, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Floppy Disks (1 of 2), undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified Floppy Disks (2 of 2), undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Invoices, 1985-1996 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Woodburner Press: International Standard Book Number, 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Woodburner Press: Phone Order Form, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Woodburner Press: Promotional Material, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Woodburner Press: Sales Accounting Figures, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Woodburner Press: Sales Tax Information, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Woodburner Press: Service Description, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Literary Productions, 1961-2003; 2
  This series is comprised of two subseries. The first, "Betty Cox's Work," includes manuscripts, notes, research material, clippings, and correspondence related to a variety of Cox's creative works such as her book Liz Carpenter: Girl from Salado and Assembly of Suspects (please note that Chapter 25 is missing from the collection). "Other," the second subseries, houses manuscripts for creative works not concretely attributable to Cox, or by other authors altogether.
  This series is in good condition.
  - Betty Cox's Work, 1971-2003; 1
    - Articles (1 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Articles (2 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Articles (3 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Articles (4 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Articles (5 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Articles (6 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Articles (7 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Articles (8 of 8), 1971-1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Prologue (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Prologue (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Preface and Chapter 1, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 1 (1 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 1 (2 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 1 (3 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 1 (4 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 2 (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 2 (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 3 (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 3 (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 3 (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 4 (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 4 (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 5 (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 5 (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 5 (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapters 5 and 6, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 6 (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 6 (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 7, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapters 7 and 8, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapters 7, 8, and 10, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 8 (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 8 (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 9 (1 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 9 (2 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 9 (3 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 10 (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 10 (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 11 (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 11 (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 12, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 13, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 14 (1 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 14 (2 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 14 (3 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 14 (4 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 15 (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 15 (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 16, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 17, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 18, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 19, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 21, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 22 (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 22 (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 23, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 24, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 26, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Chapter 27, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (1 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (2 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (3 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (4 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (5 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (6 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (7 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (8 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (9 of 15), undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (10 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (11 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (12 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (13 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (14 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Notes and Revisions (15 of 15), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Publication Queries (1 of 2), 1975 March 10-1979 July 31 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Publication Queries (2 of 2), 1975 March 10-1979 July 31 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Publication Rejections, 1979 August 9-1979 August 21 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Unidentified Manuscript Pages (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Assembly of Suspects: Unidentified Manuscript Pages (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Bricks Alive to Testify (1 of 3), 1991 May 15-1991 October 27 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bricks Alive to Testify (2 of 3), 1991 May 15-1991 October 27 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bricks Alive to Testify (3 of 3), 1991 May 15-1991 October 27 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Color of Oil: The Life of Ronald Kinnison DeFord (1 of 3), undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Color of Oil: The Life of Ronald Kinnison DeFord (2 of 3), undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Color of Oil: The Life of Ronald Kinnison DeFord (3 of 3), undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Danger at Hohokum House: Publishing Queries, 1975 December 23 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - G.W. Slept Here (1 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - G.W. Slept Here (2 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - G.W. Slept Here (3 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - G.W. Slept Here (4 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - G.W. Slept Here (5 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - G.W. Slept Here (6 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - G.W. Slept Here (7 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - G.W. Slept Here (8 of 8), undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Georgetown Mystery Manuscript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "German Dancers", 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Golden Oldies", 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - If Elected I Promise (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - If Elected I Promise (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - If Elected I Promise (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Liz Carpenter: Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Liz Carpenter: Invoices, 1994-2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Liz Carpenter: Invoices for Library Research Assistant, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Liz Carpenter: Promotional Materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Liz Carpenter: Royalty Statements, 1992-2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (1 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (2 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (3 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (4 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (5 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (6 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research (7 of 7), undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research about Tom Sutherland (1 of 5), undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research about Tom Sutherland (2 of 5), undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research about Tom Sutherland (3 of 5), undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research about Tom Sutherland (4 of 5), undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Liz Carpenter: Research about Tom Sutherland (5 of 5), undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - "Miniature Militia" (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Miniature Militia" (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Miniature Militia" (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Partials, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Publishing Queries, 1979-1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Scarecat, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - "To Bar or Not to Bar", undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - "Tux and Tails", undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - "Untamed Garden", undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Other, 1961-1996; 2
    - Aimee's Body: Chapter, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Aimee's Body: Character, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Letters Home, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Curtis, Terry: Papa and the Railroad (1 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Curtis, Terry: Papa and the Railroad (2 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Curtis, Terry: Papa and the Railroad (3 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Easter Greetings, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Mystery Writer's Workshop, 1987 May 16 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Publication Booklets (1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Publication Booklets (2 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Untitled Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Untitled Manuscript (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Untitled Manuscript (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Personal Materials, 1896-2007; 3
  The third series, Personal Materials, provides an excellent overview of Cox's life. It includes materials pertaining to her education, employment history, medical situations, finances, and her passing in 2006. It also has photographs, notes, cards, and a memoir. The dates for this series range from 1896-2007, but the bulk of the material falls between 1944 to 2006.
  Photographic print
  - Addresses, Memos, and Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Autograph Book, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Biographical: Clippings, 1972-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Biographical: Memoir (1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Biographical: Memoir (2 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Biographical: Name Change Request, 1991 November 20 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Biographical: Other, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cards (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cards (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cards (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Certificates, 1974-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1969-1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1969-1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Confirmation/Baptism, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Michelle Croft, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Eleanor James (1 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Eleanor James (2 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Daughters of the Republic of Texas Application, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Death Records: Authorization for Cremation and Disposition, 2006 August 28 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Death Records: Condolences (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Death Records: Condolences (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Death Records: Estate Settlement (1 of 3), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Death Records: Estate Settlement (2 of 3), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Death Records: Estate Settlement (3 of 3), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Death Records: Funeral/Obituary (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Death Records: Funeral/Obituary (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Death Records: Life Legacy Donation, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dragon Home, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Education: High School Diploma, 1944 July 29 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Education: Rusk School, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Education: Texas Woman's University, 1957-1969 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Education: University of Texas-Austin, 1958-1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Employment: Alpha Omega Writer's Agreement, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Employment: American-Statesman Neighborhood Reporter, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Employment: Arizona State Library Association Conference (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Employment: Arizona State Library Association Conference (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Employment: Arizona State Library Association Conference (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Employment: Author's Consultant, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Employment: Job Correspondence, 1971-1986 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Employment: Library Assistant: University of Texas, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Employment: Ocotillo Branch Library (1 of 3), 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Employment: Ocotillo Branch Library (2 of 3), 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Employment: Ocotillo Branch Library (3 of 3), 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Employment: Ocotillo Branch Library: Photographs, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Employment: Teaching Records, 1957-1982 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Employment: Texas A&M University Library, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Employment: University of Texas at Austin, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Financial Documents: Cash Flow Report, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Financial Documents: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1996-2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Financial Documents: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1996-2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Financial Documents: Invoices, 1993-2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Financial Documents: Rental Applications, 1990-2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Financial Documents: Social Security Benefits, 2004-2006 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Financial Documents: Tax Returns (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Financial Documents: Tax Returns (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Game Bag, 1973-1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence (3 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence (4 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence (5 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence (6 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence (7 of 7), 1977-2006 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Images of Russian Nobility, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)